When I was little, I would wake up at night terrified by the idea of death.
My father would comfort me with soft pets and kisses, but he would never lie.
We all die, Susie, he would say, it's normal to be scared.
He didn't try to invent a buffer between me and reality.
It took me a while to understand the power of how he guided me through those nights.
What he showed me is that courage is not an absence of fear.
Courage is fear-walking.
Neither of us knew that in ten short years he would be gone, and the time for each of
us is all too precious and all too brief.
But when our moment comes to face our fragility in that ultimate time, it will ask us, are
you agile, are you agile?
Let the moment be an unreserved yes, a yes born of a lifelong correspondence with your
own heart, and in seeing yourself, because in seeing yourself, you are also able to
see others too.
He only sustainable way forward in a fragile, beautiful world, so well-borner, and thank
you.
Thank you.